Mohammad Zaher Abualrub

Junior Full Stack Developer

About Me

I am a 20-year-old fresh graduate from Applied Science Private University. I'm a very social and active person involved in various university activities. I've competed in international and national programming competitions, and I'm currently working on mastering Full Stack Development specially Backend Development.

Education

Applied Science Private University

Bachelor of Computer Science Sep 2021 - sep2023

Projects

Github: https://github.com/abualrub03

I've done several small-scale clean code projects, most of which have been uploaded to GitHub. I developed it using several technologies, most notably .NET MVC, and using relational databases like MSSQL and adding a few features to these projects like authentications and authorizations using JWT and Claims.

Knowledge

- html ,css and Js
- SQL

Ajax

- Java
- jQuery
- Linux
- .NET Core MVC
- Git

• C++

Python

OOP

- C#
- Bootstrap
- REST APIs
- project management skills
- Web Design

Contact Info:



+962799800998



m abualrub03@outlook.com



Address: Amman Jordan



Mohammad Abualrub



abualrub03

EXPERIENCE

O Software engineering & DevOps (Internship) - Atypon May 2023 - July 2023 / 3 mos

During my second year at university, I had a very special opportunity at Atypon to be intern in the field of software engineering using Spring Boot technology using Java and DevOps principles.

Full Stack .NET Development (Internship) - Kayan HR August 2023 - Jan 2024 / 6 mos

I got the opportunity to gain practical experience in Full Stack web development and complete many projects, which provided me with huge experience in html, css, javascript, C#, .Net Core, Model-View-Controller (MVC) Design Pattern, jQuery, ASP.NET AJAX, Rest Api, SQL Server, Bootstrap (Framework) and more.

Estarta Incubator Program (Internship) - Estarta Mar 2024 - Present

For the third time, I received a more distinguished opportunity to be an intern at Estarta, as this internship includes covering all the basic principles in the world of networking, specifically the topics that branch out from the cisco certified network associate certificate (CCNA), and gaining practical experience in covering these topics.

Oracle Integration Cloud Development (Internship)

- Software Consultancy

July 2024 - Present

O.Net Full Stack Developer - OH Tech Solutions

Limited Contract
July 2024 - September 2024

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Google Developer Student Club

Achieving the first position in the Google Programming competition (Hour of Code) at the university level, based on excellence in problem-solving.

\diamond Jordanian Collegiate Programming Contest

Achieving good ranks in the Jordanian Programming Competition (JCPC), competing at the country level.

IEEE XTREME

Qualified twice in a row as a participant in the IEEE XTREME global problem-solving competition.

O NYUAD Hackathon 2024

Qualified to represent the university and Jordan in the New York University - Abu Dhabi Hackathon for Artificial Intelligence and Quantum Computing with the elite students around the world.

TEDx

- Selected by TEDx ASPU 2024 as head of event management.
- Selected by TEDx JU 2024 as Operation Manager.

English Language Olympiad - ELO

The Main Organizer twice in a row to organize the International English Language Olympiad, which is held at ASPU in partnership with Massa For International Exams, with 1,500 people attending in each edition.

○ Hult Prize

Selected by the renowned global entrepreneurial organization, Hult Prize 2024, to contribute as vice for the Campus director in the university program and selected in Hult Prize 2023 program to contribute as team member in the organizing committee.